serversub.com 2017-01-17

# ServerSub | Dedicated, Virtual Servers, Security Solutions

## **Privacy** Policy

In an effort to protect our clients and site visitors privacy and rights, ServerSub.com has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ServerSub.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User"). 

* * *

## The **Information** We Collect

ServerSub.com collects personally identifiable information from Users through online forms for ordering products and services. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. 

* * *

## How **We Use** Information

ServerSub.com may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by ServerSub.com and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with ServerSub.com and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.   
At no time will ServerSub.com's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without your prior consent, except that we will disclose the information we collect to third parties when, in our good faith judgment, we are obligated to do so under applicable laws. 

* * *

## How do we **protect** your Information

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.  
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  
All transactions are processed through gateway providers and are not stored or processed on our servers. 

* * *

## **Cookies**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  

## We use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

* * *

## **Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

* * *

## **Changes** on Privacy Policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ServerSub may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. ServerSub encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a account with us, you can also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

* * *

## **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

> ServerSub.com  
>  __364 E Main Street,  
>     Suite 1011, Middletown,  
>     DE 19709, United States
> 
> __info [@] ServerSub.com
